Guide to the Eugene Sonnenberg Boerner papers, 1894-1968.
Boerner, Eugene Sonnenberg papers
- Series 3: Business Papers
  - "Parade of Modern Perennials", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Short article on new perennials growing in company garden
  - "Parade of Modern Roses - 1940 Edition", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Perennials", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Perennials", 1941; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Perennials", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Perennials", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Perennials", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Perennials", 1943; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Perennials for 1939", 1939; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Perennials for the Garden", 1944; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "The Perfect Rose Climate", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Pinocchio's Famous Family", 1951; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Planting & Germination of Seeds", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Plant Patent", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Flower growing (plant patents)
  - "Progress in Rose Hybridizing", 1949; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "The Pruning of Roses", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Queens to Reign in Every Garden", 1950; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing, Jackson and Perkins Co.
  - "Refurbishing the Border", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Report on Some of the Newer Roses", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "A Resume of Budded Plants", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "The Rose", 1941; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing (History)
  - "The Rose Capitol of the United States", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Rose Culture Practical Hobby", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Rose Europe and the World War", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    World War II, rose growing
  - "Rose of the Future", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "The Rose of the Future", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "The Rose of the Future", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing (Floribundia variety)
  - "Roses", 1947; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses", 1947; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Rcses After the War", 1947; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses", 1951; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing (Baltimore, Maryland)
  - "Roses and the World War", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses for 1942", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses for 1952", 1952; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses for Color", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses for the New Homeowners", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses for Your Home", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses in 1954", 1953; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses in Europe", 1948; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses in Europe", 1947; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses in Europe", 1949; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Roses in the World War", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing (Spin), rose growing (Holland), rose growing (Italy), rose growing (France )
  - "Roses of Today", 1950; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Rose Starlite", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Secretary's Corner", 1941; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Some of tte Roses for 1944-1945", 1944; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Spreading European War Makes U.S. Rose Capitol", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Spring Care of Roses", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Started Budded Rose Plants for 1942", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Summer Care for Fall Bloom", 1944; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "The Time to Plant Roses", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Trends in Roses", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing (history)
  - "Your Garden arid the War", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Gardens and Gardening
  - "The Versatile Floribunda Rose", 1951; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing (Florabundas variety)
  - "The Versatile Floribunda Roses", 1951; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Victory Garden Program", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Flower growing; Victory Garden
  - "Victory Gardens", 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Gardens arid Gardening
  - "Winter Covering of Roses", Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Winter Covering of Tree Roses", 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1939; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1939; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    World's Fair
  - No Title, 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Flower growing (perennials )
  - No Title, 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Travel (Pre World War II Europe)
  - No Title, 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing (experimentation)
  - No Title, 1941; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Flower growing (delphiniums)
  - No Title, 1941; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1941; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Newark (Wayne Co.), rose growing
  - No Title, 1941; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1941; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Flower growing, Victory Gardens
  - No Title, 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Victory Gardens; flower growing (flower shows); Jackson & Perkins
  - No Title, 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Newark (Wayne Co.); rose growing
  - No Title, 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1942; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Jackson & Perkins; flower growing (flower shows)
  - No Title, 1943; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Discussion of the Finger Lakes Hardy strain of delphinium; flower growing (delphiniums )
  - No Title, 1943; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1943; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Flower growing (insect distinction)
  - No Title, 1943; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1944; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1945; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1945; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1946; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1947; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1947; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing (post war activities)
  - No Title, 1947; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1949; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1940; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1950; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1951; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    All American Rose Selection
  - No Title, 1953; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, 1956; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Newark (Wayne Co.)
  - No Title, 1962; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - No Title, Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
    Rose growing and marketing
  - No Title, Undated; Typescript Article (Box 64)
  - "Rose History", Undated; Notes (Box 64)
    Rose growing ( Research), rose growing (history)
  - Photograph Scrapbook & Miscellaneous Photos, Undated; Eugene S. Boerner; Scrapbook (Box 65)
  - Slides, 1940-1966 (Box 66)
  - Slides, 1937-1966 (Box 67)
    Gene's Landing; Belgium, Bermuda, Caribbean, England
  - Slides, 1937-1965 (Box 68)
    England, France, Germany
  - Slides, 1937-1965 (Box 69)
    Germany, Holland, Ireland, Italy, Newfoundland, Spain, Labrador and Greenland, Switzerland
  - Slides, 1943-1964 (Box 70)
    Arizona, California, Delaware, District of Columbia, Florida, Oklahoma, Oregon, Pennsylvania, Virginia
  - Slides, 1939-1962 (Box 71)
  - Slides, Undated (Box 72)
    Roses (photographs); West, place unknown 1961; Jackson & Perkins Gardens (photographs )
  - Movie film, Undated; Film Strips (Box 73)
    "Rose Festival", "Planting Roses", "Million Dollar Rose", "Arranging Roses", "Rose Breeding", "Modern Roses on Parade"
  - Phonograph records and tape recordings, 1945-1955; Phonograph Records and Tape Recordings (Box 73)
    Song " A l l America Rose" n.d.; "Fall Planting of Roses" "Rose Festival 1945"; Home Gardner; Farm News-Interview 1951; Phil Alamp; All-America Rose Selection n.d. Ma Perkins radio show 1953
  - Material, Undated (Box 74)